他拉起他的雪橇  吹起他的口哨
He sprang to his sleigh to his team gave a whistle
他们奔驰而去  如同蓟草的细毛
And away they all flew Like the down of a thistle
但我听他喊出  就在他要消失飞去之前
But I heard him exclaim Ere he drove out of sight
"祝大家圣诞快乐
"Merry Christmas to all
享受一个美好的夜晚"
And to all a good night."
哇  真是太棒了
Wow! That was great!
真的是你自己创作的吗
You really wrote that?
没错
Uhhuh
再见了  精灵们  我要去塔尔萨了
Say goodbye,elves. I'm off to Tulsa.
我不敢相信你居然不在这里过圣诞节
I can't believe you won't be here for Christmas.
你真的不回来吗
You're really not coming back?
我们有很多报告
We have this paperwork
都要在年底的时候归档
that needs to be filed by the end of the year.
如果我不去做  我就会被炒鱿鱼
If I don't get it done,I'll be fired.
真是不公平
It's so unfair.
你根本就不喜欢你的工作
You don't even like your job.
那又如何  谁喜欢自己的工作
So. Who does?
我喜欢我的  我爱我的工作
I like my job.  I love my job.
我等不及要回去上班了
I can't wait to go back to work.
我对恐龙就是百看不厌
I can't get enough dinosaurs.
我很抱歉没有办法回来
I'm sorry I won't be here.
平常没有办法见到你已经够难受了
It's hard enough not seeing you during the week..
但是圣诞节
but for Christmas..
如果你不得不去做  我会谅解
If this is what you have to do,I understand.
谢谢
Thanks.
新年当天见
I'll see you New Year's Day.
你除夕不回来吗
You're not gonna be here New Year's Eve?
我没有提过吗  没有
Did I not mention that?  No.
那大家晚安了
And to all a good night!
《老友记》  第九季 第10集  在塔尔萨过圣诞
Friends S09E10 The One With Christmas In Tulsa
好了大家  我知道今晚是平安夜
All right,everybody. I know it is Christmas Eve..
你们都想要跟家人在一起
and you'd rather be with family,
但是也不可以写
but there is no call for writing..
"去你的  宾先生"
"Screw you,Mr. Bing"
贴在我的椅子后面
on the back of my chair.
对了  你们叫我钱德勒就可以了
By the way,you can all call me Chandler.
嘿  嘿  你跑哪去了
Hey.  Hey. Where you been?
我去看了下
I was checking out
三楼那家保险公司的圣诞派对
that insurance company's Christmas party on three.
真的是很美
It was really beautiful.
他们有很多装饰品  一颗很大的圣诞树
They have decorations and this huge tree.
然后我就想  去他们的
And I just thought,to hell with them,
我们竟然要工作
we have to work.
所以我偷了他们的火腿
So I stole their ham.
听到了没  你们或许没有跟家人在一起
Hear that? You may not be with your families..
但是至少这里也可以闻到过节的火腿味
but at least it's gonna smell like ham in here.
我的小孩现在正在表演话剧
My kid's in a play right now.
来  我知道要怎么鼓舞你们
You know what? I know what will cheer you up.
我跟纽约那边的人谈过了
I had a talk with the boys in New York.
我告诉他们你们是如何辛勤地工作
I told them about all your hard work you've been doing.
所以你们可能都会得到一些圣诞奖金
and that a little Christmas bonus may be in order.
已经以您的名义把一项捐款
"A donation has been made in your name
捐赠给纽约市芭蕾舞团
to the New York City Ballet."
那就像是进了你们的口袋一样啊
Well,that's like money in your pocket.
好了  你们一定要逼我说吗
All right,you want me to say it?
真是烂透了
This sucks.
在这里真是烂  这份工作真是烂
Being here sucks. This work sucks!
现在有点像是圣诞节了
Now it feels like Christmas.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
至少你们今晚都可以回家
At least you get to go home
跟家人在一起
and be with your families tonight.
我只能回到空荡荡的旅馆房间
I have to go to an empty hotel room
然后躺在一张很有卫生问题的床单上
and lay down.. on a very questionable bedspread.
然后明天早上
Then tomorrow morning,
你们都可以在自己家里过节
you get to have Christmas in your own houses.
顺便提一下  你们没有一个邀请我去
Which,by the way,none of you have invited me to.
你可以来我家  不用了  谢谢
You can come to my house.  No,thanks.
真是精彩的鼓舞发言  谢谢
It was a nice pep talk.  Thanks.
我是真的有在想要成为激励演说家
I'm actually thinking about becoming a motivational speaker.
那如果你现在在家
So if you were home right now,
你会是在做什么呢
what would you be doing?
一般的圣诞节活动  你知道的
Typical Christmassy stuff,you know.
我们过节的方式是很传统的
Our holidays are pretty traditional.
有一首十分特殊的节庆歌曲
So here's a very special holiday song..
是我为一些对我很重要的人写的
that I wrote for some very important people to me.
我去店里坐在圣诞老人膝头
Went to the store Sat on Santa's lap
要他送一堆礼物给我朋友
Asked him to bring my friends all kinds of crap
他说你只需要帮他们写首歌
Said all you need is To write them a song
这首歌你们没听过  别想跟着我唱
Now you haven't heard it yet So don't try to sing along
不要跟我一起唱
No,don't sing along
莫妮卡  光明节快乐
Monica,Monica Have a happy Hannukah
我看到圣诞老人
Saw Santa Claus
他要我向罗斯问好
He said hello to Ross
请告诉乔伊
And please tell Joey
圣诞节将瑞雪纷飞
Christmas will be snowy
还有瑞秋和钱德勒
And Rachel and Chandler
大家圣诞快乐
Happy holidays,everybody.
菲比  去检查厨房
Phoebe,look in the kitchen.
我去看衣橱后面
I'll look in the back closet.
我可以节省你们的时间  女士们
I can save you time,ladies.
我就在这里
I'm right here.
钱德勒  你何不出去一下
Yeah. Chandler,why don't you take a walk.
此事跟你没有关系
This doesn't concern you.
我们在找莫妮卡准备的圣诞礼物
We are looking for our Christmas presents from Monica.
什么  实在太过分了
What? That's terrible.
不不  我们每年都这样做的
No,no. We do it every year.
那这样就不过分了吗
Well,that makes it not terrible.
是啊  我们从来没有找到过
No. Yeah,we never find them.
她总是高明过我们  她狡猾又
She's always bested us,that wily..
顽皮
minx.
别担心  我们在这边找一个小时
Don't worry. We're gonna search here for an hour..
然后再过去乔伊家找  好吗
and then we'll go to Joey's and search. Okay?
不  不好
No,not okay.
你们不可以找莫妮卡的礼物
You can't look for Monica's presents.
我们一定要  不  你们不需要这样
No,we have to.  No,you don't have to.
你们不可以  因为我也住在这里
And you can't,because I live here too.
那你应该帮我们找  为什么
Well,then you should look with us.  Why?
钱德勒  你难道不烦恼要买什么
Chandler, Aren't you worried about
圣诞礼物给莫妮卡吗
what to get Monica for Christmas?
不担心  我已想好一个很棒的礼物要给她
No,I have a great idea for a present for her.
就这样  才想法而已吗
That's it? "A great idea"?
那是不够的
That's not enough.
万一她送你的是一个很棒的礼物
What if she gets you a great present..
两个中等的礼物  还有很多的小礼物
two medium presents and lots of little presents..
而你只送她一个很棒的礼物
and you got her one great present?
那会让她很伤心的
That's gonna make her feel bad.
你为什么要那样对待她呢  钱德勒
Why would you do that to her, Chandler?
为什么  为什么
Why? Why?
如果我帮忙  我们就可以更快找到
If I helped,we could find them faster!
没错
Right.
我找到一个了
We have a live one!
是梅西百货的袋子
It's a Macy's bag!
这是要给谁的
Who's it for?
亲爱的衰人们  你们真的认为
"Dear Losers: Do you really think
我会将礼物藏在沙发下面吗
I'd hide presents under the couch?
附注  钱德勒
P.S. Chandler,
我就知道  她们会攻破你
I knew they'd break you."
瑞秋  这些是给你的
Rach,these are for you.
雨刷  但是我根本就没有车子
Wiper blades. I don't even have a car.
是没有
No,
但此款芳香剂有新车的味道
but with this newcar smell,
你会以为你有的
you'll think you do.
好了  菲比  轮到你了
Okay,Phoebe,your turn.
马桶座盖纸
Toilet seat covers!
你们是趁我给车加气的时候
Is that what you were doing
你们去买的吧
while I was getting gas?
你们俩
You guys.
还有给罗斯  甜食先生
And for Ross,Mr. Sweet Tooth.
你们送我可乐  还有柠檬口味
You got me a cola drink?  And.. a lemonlime!
噢  这  这礼真是太大了
Well,this.. This is too much.
我觉得我应该再送你一件毛衣
I feel like I should get you another sweater.
最后一位
And last but not least..
是罗纹保险套  让你得到绝顶满足
They're ribbed,for your pleasure.
嘿  本
Well,hey,Ben?
要不要节日犰狳来告诉你
What if the Holiday Armadillo told you
光明节的由来呢
all about the Festival of Lights?
好啊
Cool!
来吧  本
Come on,Ben.
很多年以前
Years and years ago,
有一群叫做马加比家族的人
there were these people called the Maccabees!
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas!
圣诞老人
Santa!
你在这里做什么呢  圣诞老人
What are you doing here,Santa?
噢  我是来看我的老朋友本的
Well,I'm here to see my old buddy Ben.
你在这里做什么呢
What are you doing here..
奇怪的乌龟男
weird turtleman?
我是节日犰狳  你的半犹太血统朋友
I'm the Holiday Armadillo,your partJewish friend.
你要我过来送些礼物给本的
You sent me here to give Ben some presents.
记得吗
Remember?
什么
What?
本  你何不去打开更多的礼物
Ben,why don't you open some more presents.
圣诞老人  犰狳跟我要去厨房谈谈
Santa,the armadillo and I will have a talk in the kitchen.
我以为这辈子都不可能说这样的话
There's a sentence I never thought I'd say.
你在做什么呢
What are you doing?
你打电话告诉大家说
You called and said
你找不到圣诞老人的服装
you had trouble finding a Santa costume..
所以我跟公司的同事借了这一套
so I borrowed one from a guy at work.
谢谢你  但是你得离开
Thank you,but you gotta leave.
为什么  因为
Why?  Because..
我终于让他对犹太光明节有兴趣了
I'm finally getting him excited about Hanukkah.
而你破坏了这一切
And you're wrecking it.
但我还没有机会
But I didn't get to
把我的肚子像果冻那样晃来晃去
shake my belly like a bowl full of jelly.
我很抱歉  钱德勒
I'm sorry,Chandler,
但是这对我真的很重要
but this is really important to me.
好的  没关系  我去还这套衣服
Okay,fine. I'll give the suit back.
你觉得可以把这套衣服多留一晚吗
Hey,you think you can keep it another night?
圣诞老人 不是吧
Santa? Really?
是啊  可以吗
Yeah,is that okay?
你爸爸有扮过圣诞老人吗
Did your dad ever dress up like Santa?
没有  那就没问题了
No.  Then it's okay!
知道吗  你们大家
You know what,everybody?
回家去  你们应该跟家人在一起
Go home. You should be with your families.
我们要在除夕夜工作就已经够糟了
It's bad enough we're working New Year's Eve.
我没有告诉大家除夕夜的事吗
Did I not tell anyone about New Year's Eve?
好了  听着  回去
All right,look,go.
回家去  好吗  圣诞快乐
Go home,okay? Merry Christmas.
圣诞快乐  世界和平
Merry Christmas.  Peace on earth.
再见
Bye.
很好  快走  一群好人
Good. Godspeed,good people.
你不打算走吗
You're not gonna go?
不  我不能留你一个人在这里
No. I couldn't leave you alone.
谢谢
Thanks.
除此之外  我得要等到
Besides,I can't leave until
楼下的派对都结束了我才能走
that Christmas party downstairs clears out.
有一些气坏了的保险员
There are some pissedoff insurance people
正在找那条火腿
looking for that ham.
钱德勒·宾
Chandler Bing.
嗨  亲爱的  我们全部都在这里
Hi,honey. We're all here.
我们想要祝你圣诞快乐
We want to wish you a merry Christmas.
圣诞快乐  圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas!  Merry Christmas!
圣诞快乐  我想念你们
Merry Christmas. I miss you guys.
很难受吗  每个人都在认真工作吗
So is it horrible? Is everybody working really hard?
嗯  没有  只有我跟温蒂
Well,no,it's just me and Wendy.
温蒂  听起来像是女生的名字
Wendy? That sounds like a girl's name.
就是女生  我没有提过她吗
It is. Did I not tell you about her?
就跟你没有说除夕夜要加班一样
About the time you told me about New Year's Eve.
大家去哪了  我让他们回家了
Where's everybody else?  I sent them home.
你真是好老板  她漂亮吗
You are such a good boss. Is she pretty?
快点回答  快点回答
Answer faster. Answer faster.
我不知道
I don't know.
回答高明点  回答高明点
Answer better. Answer better.
我没有那样想过她
I don't think of her that way.
我是说  她是我同事
I mean,she's a colleague.
她在那边是做什么的
What does she do there?
她是区域副总
She's regional vice president.
她在我"下面" 她什么
She's just below me.  She did what?
是职位在我下面
Below me.
等一下  温蒂是那个
Wait,is Wendy the
奥克拉荷马州小姐选美亚军吗
runnerup Miss Oklahoma?
什么
What?!
嗯  她没有赢得冠军
Well,she didn't win.
好了  或许我应该让你
All right,maybe I should let you..
跟奥克拉荷马第二漂亮的女生
and the second prettiest girl in Oklahoma
继续工作了
get back to work.
那一年第二漂亮的
Second prettiest that year.
以奥克拉荷马全部的女生来说  她或许
Of all the girls in Oklahoma,she's probably..
钱德勒  快闭嘴
Chandler,stop talking.
亲爱的  根本没什么需要担心的
Honey,there's really nothing to worry about.
好的  我是说真的
Okay.  I'm serious.
好的
Okay.
圣诞快乐  圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.  Merry Christmas.
你们大家圣诞快乐  圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas,you guys.  Merry Christmas.
我老婆打招呼  谈得愉快吗
The wife says hi.  Fun conversation?
她有一种奇怪的想法  认为
Well,she's just got this weird idea that..
因为我们两个单独在一起
because you and I are alone
所以会有事情发生
something's gonna happen.
真的吗
Really?
那样会很糟糕吗
Would that be so terrible?
我现在担心的事或许不对
This is probably the wrong thing to be worrying about..
但是你把火腿沾上我唯一的领带了
but you're getting ham on my only tie.
走开  小妞  小妞
Back off,missy!  Missy?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不习惯女孩子对我采取行动
I'm not used to girls making passes at me.
等一下  我在奥克拉荷马算性感的吗
Wait a minute. Am I sexy in Oklahoma?
对我而言是的  不不  不
You are to me.  No. No. No!
听着  我已经结婚了
Look,I'm married.
那又如何  我也结婚了
So? I'm married.
我的婚姻很幸福
I'm happily married.
那是什么样的感觉呢
What's that like?
是的  我很抱歉  但是
Right. So I'm sorry,but..
不是吧  婚姻很幸福
Seriously? Happily married?
所以刚才那通电话叫做幸福
So that phone call before,that was happy?
你知道  长期分开是很不容易的
Well,look,it's not easy to spend this much time apart.
她有点神经质也是正常的
She's entitled to be a little paranoid.
而且针对这件事  她猜对了
Or,in this case,right on the money.
她很好  漂亮又聪明
You know,she's amazing and beautiful and smart.
而且如果她现在在这里
And if she were here right now,
她一定会海扁你一顿的
she'd kick your ass.
听着  你是个好人
Look,you're a really nice person,
除了会偷火腿和偷情
hamstealing and adultery aside.
但是我跟我老婆的感情很好
But what I have with my wife is pretty great.
所以我们之间是不可能的
So nothing's ever gonna happen between us.
好的  让我问你一件事
Okay,let me ask you something.
如果你跟你老婆感情很好
If what you and your wife have is so great..
那你怎么会跟我一起过圣诞节呢
then why are you spending Christmas with me?
今晚你是这屋子里最漂亮的女人
You were the most beautiful woman in the room tonight.
真的吗  开什么玩笑
Really?  Are you kidding?
绝大多数场合下  你都是最漂亮的女人
You're the most beautiful woman in most rooms.
这是怎么回事  我们刚刚亲吻了
What's going on? You and I just made out.
我们在亲吻  嗯  以后不会有了
You and I are making out?  Well,not anymore.
但是我们从来不会那样的
But we don't do that.
我知道  我只是觉得那可能会很好玩
I know. I just thought it would be fun.
你有多醉呢
How drunk are you?
醉到让我想这样做
Drunk enough that I wanna do this.
但又没有醉到让你觉得
Not so drunk that you should feel
占我便宜是有罪恶感的
guilty about taking advantage.
真是醉的恰到好处
That's a perfect amount.
你知道什么很奇怪吗  什么
You know what's weird?  What?
就是这竟然一点都不怪  我知道
This doesn't feel weird.  I know.
你真是接吻高手
You're a really good kisser.
嗯  我吻过超过四个女人
Well,I have kissed over four women.
你想要到棉被底下吗  好的
You wanna get under the covers?  Okay.
哇  你真快
Wow,you are really fast.
得到你的赞赏  让我"性心"大增
It bodes well for me that speed impresses you.
我们将要看到彼此裸体了 是的
We're gonna see each other naked.  Yep.
你想要一起看吗  数到三
You want to do it at the same time?  Count of three?
一   二
One.  Two.
三
Three.
我想我可以很肯定的说
Well,I think it's safe to say that
我们的友情已经完全被摧毁了
our friendship is effectively ruined.
反正我们本来也没有很友好
We weren't that close anyway.
你真的要跟那个男护士约会吗
Are you really gonna go out with that nurseman?
嗯  反正你跟我只是玩玩而已
Well,you and I are just goofing around.
所以我想  我也可以跟他玩玩
I thought,why not just goof around with him?
我不知道你有没有查过字典
I don't know if you've ever looked up the term
"玩玩"是什么意思
"goofing around" in the dictionary.
我有查过
Well,I have.
专业的解释就是两个朋友
And the technical definition is two friends..
很在乎彼此  然后又做了很棒的爱
who care a lot about each other and have amazing sex..
而且想要花更多的时间在一起
and just want to spend more time together.
如果你那新版的字典
If you have this newfangled dictionary
让你对我生气
that gets you mad at me..
那我们就只好
then we have to,you know,
帮你买我这本原版的字典
get you my original dictionary.
我真是不会说话
I am so bad at this.
我认为你比你想的要棒
I think you're better than you think you are.
真的吗  好的  所以如果
Really? Okay. So if..?
知道什么时候该停
Know when to stop.
我感觉到我应该停了
I sensed that I should stop.
所以我们没事了吗  是的
So we're okay?  Yeah.
别跳那个舞  好的
Don't do the dance.  Right.
叫我怎么结婚
I can't get married
没有旧物  新物
without something old,something new..
借来之物  蓝色之物（美国婚礼习俗）
something borrowed,something blue.
好的  好的  好吧
Okay,okay. Okay.
这是蓝色的  而且是新的
Here's something blue and new.
你真是有效率  我爱你
You are so efficient. I love you.
我们走吧  不不  等一下
Let's go.  No,no,wait!
我们需要旧物
We need something old.
好的  我钱包里有个保险套
Okay. I have a condom in my wallet
从我12岁起就放里面了
that I've had since I was 12.
那也可以的
That'll work!
我可不觉得
I don't think so.
好了  现在我们需要一个借来的东西
Okay. Now we just need something borrowed.
这个  拿去  这是偷窃
Here,just take this.  That's stealing.
我们会归还的  塞到你礼服里
We'll bring it back. Just put it under your dress.
好了  一件一件来
Okay,one thing at a time.
听着
Listen..
我一直在想
I've been thinking.
我要求把你所有的积蓄花在
It's not fair for me to ask you
我们的婚礼上   是很不公平的事
to spend all of your money on our wedding.
我是说  你很辛苦工作才存到的
I mean,you work.. You work really hard for that.
好吧  只是工作  没有辛苦
Well,you work for that.
听着  我也有想过  而且
Look,I've thought about it too. And..
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想我们应该将所有钱花在婚礼上
I think we should spend all of the money on the wedding.
真的吗
You do?
是的  我强烈要求那样做
Yeah. I'm putting my foot down.
听着  我求婚的时候
Yeah,look,when I proposed..
我告诉你我会尽一切努力让你快乐
I told you that I would do anything to make you happy.
而如果一个完美的婚礼
And if having the perfect wedding
能够让你快乐  那么
makes you happy,then..
那就是我们要做的
Then that's what we're gonna do.
你真的好贴心
You are so sweet.
但是等一下  那我们
But wait. What about our..?
那我们将来的计划呢
What about the future and stuff?
管他什么将来的计划
Forget about the future and stuff.
我们只生两个小孩就好了
So we only have two kids.
然后我们再挑我们喜欢的那一个
You know,we'll pick our favorite,
送他去念大学
and that one will get to go to college.
你都想好了吗  是啊
You've thought about that?  Yeah.
我们要生几个小孩呢
How many kids were we gonna have?
4个  一个儿子  双胞胎女儿
Four. A boy,twin girls..
然后再生一个儿子
and another boy.
你还想过什么呢  嗯
What else did you think about?  Well..
比如我们要住的地方  你知道的
stuff like where we'd live,you know.
在市中心外面的小房子
Like a small place outside the city
我们的孩子可以学习骑脚踏车
where our kids could ride bikes and stuff.
我们可以养只猫  颈圈上有个铃铛
And we could have a cat that had a bell on its collar..
然后每次他经过小猫咪门的时候
and we could hear it every time
我们就可以听到铃铛声
it ran through the little kitty door.
我们会在车库上面留一间房间
We'd have an apartment over the garage
让乔伊在那里养老
where Joey could grow old.
你知道吗
You know what?
我不需要大型豪华的婚礼了
I don't.. I don't want a big,fancy wedding.
你当然需要  不
Sure you do.  No.
我想要你刚刚说的一切
I want everything that you've just said.
我只想要结婚
I want a marriage.
你确定吗
You sure?
我好爱你  我也爱你
I love you so much.  I love you.
我太喜欢了
I love it!
真的吗  你不会退回去吗
Really? You're not gonna return it?
嗯  不会马上退
Well,not this second.
嘿  你们瞧  下雪了
Hey,look,you guys. It's snowing!
哇  真漂亮  哇  真的是
Wow,it's so beautiful.  Wow,it really is.
温蒂是胖女生的名字
Wendy's a fatgirl name.
我们还没有说够吗
Aren't we done with that?
好啦  不说了 我们来聊雪
Okay,fine. Fine. Let's talk about snow.
你们觉得塔尔萨在下雪吗
Do you think it's snowing in Tulsa
而我老公正在影印机上面做爱
where my husband's having sex on a copier?
嘿  噢 我的天
Hey.  Oh,my God.
瞧瞧  真是圣诞奇迹
Look at that. That's a Christmas miracle!
你在这里做什么呢
What are you doing here?
我想要跟你在一起
I wanted to be with you.
我好想你
I missed you so much.
嘿  你最想念谁呢  莫妮卡
Hey,hey. Who'd you miss the most?  Monica.
知道了
Gotcha.
我再也不要离开你了
I never want to leave you again.
你不是说离开会被炒鱿鱼的吗
I thought if you left,you'd get fired.
他们没有办法炒我鱿鱼的
Turns out they can't fire me.
因为我不干了
Because I quit.
什么  什么  你真的辞职了
What?  What? You..? You really quit your job?
是的  那是份愚蠢的工作
Yeah. It was a stupid job,
而我无法忍受离开你
and I could not stand leaving you.
我为什么要当那个唯一
Why should I be the only one
必须做他不想要做的事的人
who doesn't do what he really wants to do?
那你真的想做什么呢
Well,what do you really wanna do?
我还没想清楚
I have not thought this through.
噢 我的天
Oh,my God.
我知道  我应该先跟你讨论的
I know. I should've talked to you first about it.
不  我想如果这是你想要的
No,I think that this is what you wanna do.
我认为这很棒
I think it's great!
谢谢
Thanks.
钱德勒  你能够回来
Chandler,your being here
是我有过的最棒的圣诞礼物了
is the best Christmas present I could ever imagine.
现在给我真正的礼物  好
Now give me my real gift.  Yeah.
谢谢  这里  分给大家
Thank you.  Here,pass those around.
"一项捐款已经以您的名义
"A donation has been made in your name
捐赠给纽约市芭蕾舞团"
to the New York City Ballet."
你怎么会知道我要这个呢
How did you know?
什么  你在开玩笑吗
What? Are you kidding?
我不能退还这个的
I can't return this.
该是我们关怀别人的时候了
It's time we started thinking about other people.
除此之外  这份礼物上面也写了
And besides,this gift still says,
"我爱你们"
"I love you guys."
我的上面写"给莉莉安·迈尔"
Mine says,"To Lillian Myers."
我可是失业了
I don't have a job.
精算师  不行
Actuary? No.
簿记员  不行
Bookkeeper? No.
跳艳舞的
Topless dancer?
嗨  你知道我刚才意识到什么吗
Hey,you know what I just realized?
你是家里唯一的收入来源
You are the sole wage earner.
你是这个家的家长
You are the head of the household.
我什么都没做  我是被供养的小白脸
I don't do anything. I'm a kept man!
没错
You are.
亲爱的  这里有20块
Honey,here's 20 bucks.
你明天自己买点东西
Go buy yourself something pretty
我要去上班
while I'm at work tomorrow.